https://www.algomau.ca/privacy-policy/

Admissions Requirements
Algoma University Homestay Program (AUHP)
Academic Advising and Registration
Algoma Mentorship Program (AMP)
Chancellor
Common University Data Ontario (CUDO)
Admissions Requirements
Algoma University Homestay Program (AUHP)
Academic Advising and Registration
Algoma Mentorship Program (AMP)
Chancellor
Common University Data Ontario (CUDO)
Access to Information
A request for information contained in our records may be made formally under the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act.  However, it is not always necessary to file an official request as Algoma University provides information to the public through a number of its academic and administrative units. Informal inquiries are welcomed.
Formal requests for access to information are made under the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act.  This request must be in writing, accompanied by a $5 application fee, and provide enough detail to allow the University to identify the records.  All requests must also include contact information including name, address, and day-time telephone number.
To begin the process, you may contact us by emailing FIPPA@algomau.ca.
For more information and details on the request procedure, please read through our Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Policy (PDF).
Protection of Privacy
Algoma University takes the protection of the personal information seriously, and aims to collect only the specific personal information that is needed for the operation of the University.
Personal information will be used, maintained, disclosed, and disposed of in accordance with the applicable provincial or federal legislation.
If you have a concern or questions about the protection of your personal information, please contact us by emailing privacy@algomau.ca.
Future. Focused.
Sign up to learn more about what sets Algoma apart and to get application advice sent right to your inbox.
All fields opposite are required tosubmit your interest.
First Name*Last Name*Email Address*
Telephone Number*Which campus are you interested in?*SELECTSault Ste. MarieBramptonTimminsNot Sure
Submit
